my-free.website 2015-10-18

# Privacy Policy for WebsiteBuilder.com - Privacy - WebsiteBuilder

**Updated and Effective as of August 1, 2014**

This Privacy Policy applies to WZ (UK) Ltd operating as Website Builder and use of personally identifying information ("Personal Information") that we may gather when you visit our Website, purchase, license, or Use Website Builder Products or Services, or contact us. By Using Website Builder Products or Services, you expressly consent to the collection, processing, and use of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy. 

Our Terms and Conditions of Use discuss how we handle, encrypt, and protect the data you choose to store on our servers (and any related data) ("Website Data"), as well as other matters. All provisions of the Terms and Conditions of Use are incorporated into this document by reference. 

####  **Definitions**

All of the terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as are defined in our Terms and Conditions of Use. 

####  **Why Website Builder Collects Personal Information**

Website Builder collects your Personal Information at a variety of points, including when you place an order, add a new product or update, register a website, request services, upload Website Data, confer with one of our customer support technicians, or take part in other activities on our Website. During these interactions we will collect Personal Information relevant to your transaction with Website Builder, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, e-mail address, employment information, and credit card, banking or billing information, along with information about the Website Builder Products or Services you license, such as the activation code, date of purchase, and information relating to a support issue. Website Builder will use your Personal Information to send you messages through desktop alerts, SMS/Text messaging, email, etc. concerning updates to Website Builder Products or Services. Please be aware that if you choose not to provide us with your Personal Information, we may not be able to, or may choose not to, make Website Builder Products or Services available to you. 

####  **Regarding Children**

Website Builder Products or Services are not marketed to or intended for use by individuals who cannot legally bind a contract. Accordingly, Website Builder does not intentionally gather any Personal Information about visitors or customers who are under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18 or otherwise lack the capacity to enter into a binding contract, do not use our Website or services yourself. If Website Builder becomes aware that we have collected information from someone under the age of 18, such information will be deleted immediately. 

####  **Cookies and Other Technologies**

(a) Website Builder uses "cookies" and other technologies to collect data that enable us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Website. Cookies are files sent to your browser and stored on your computer, the type of cookies that Website Builder uses are login, authentication and tracking. If you do not want Website Builder to send cookies to your browser, you can set your browser options to reject cookies or to notify you when a Website tries to put a cookie into your browser software. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use some features of Website Builder Products or Services. 

(b) Website Builder gathers general information about visits to our Website, the files you upload to your website, the configuration of your website and your computer’s interaction with Website Builder, and stores this information in log files. Website Builder uses this information to understand traffic and downloads on our Website, enabling us to improve the site, provide the best online experience possible, and improve our ability to serve our customers. 

(c) Use of Remarketing with Google Analytics and Google Adwords 

Website Builder stores cookies on our website which captures information about page visits. This information is anonymous and Website Builder uses this information internally to deliver the most effective content to our visitors. Information from the cookies is used to gauge page popularity, analyse traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. Website Builder does not require that you accept cookies, however, some functionality of our website or service may be disabled and not work correctly if you decline to accept cookies. Website Builder never gives away information about our users. If you choose to e-mail us and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, Website Builder will use this information only to respond to your inquiry. Website Builder will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose that information to third parties unless such disclosure is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Policy, by law or a policy or notice contained or associated with a specific Website Builder product or service. Website Builder uses analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Site visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Google has additional information available about their [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746), [Policies](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=143465), and [Restrictions](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=178363). 

####  **Sharing Your Personal Information**

Website Builder will not provide unaffiliated third parties with access to your email address or other contact information. Website Builder or the Website Builder Affiliates may, from time to time, share with you information about other products and services that we think you may find to be of interest. If you wish to change the types of communications you receive from us, you may do so by modifying your profile at www.Website Builder.com, by emailing your request to us at [support@websitebuilder.com](mailto:support@websitebuilder.com), or by clicking on an appropriate link in any Website Builder email communication to you. 

Website Builder may disclose your Personal Information to third parties if we believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with a law, regulation, or governmental or judicial warrant, rule, or order; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Website Builder; (3) enforce the Website Builder Terms and Conditions of Use and/or this Privacy Policy. Website Builder may also provide access to your Website Data to government authorities if Website Builder suspects or believes that the data contains child pornography or other prohibited data, or that the data or the Website Builder Products or Services are being used for illegal purposes. Website Builder will provide access to your Website Data to your surviving spouse and/or your executor upon presentation of a death certificate and identification which Website Builder reasonably believes to be valid and sufficient, or in response to a court order, warrant, subpoena or other judicial or administrative legal process. 

####  **How We Communicate with You**

Website Builder may, from time to time, send you emails, or desktop alerts or other communications containing the following types of information: notifications of detected problems with your service; notifications concerning the expiration of your account; activity status reports; service and software upgrade notices; notices concerning new or related products or services from Website Builder or other providers, enhancements, and price changes, notifications regarding suspected unlawful or inappropriate use, and requests for feedback on your Website Builder Products or Services. 

####  **Security for Your Personal Information**

Website Builder has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your Personal Information in our customer database. Personal Information provided to Website Builder is stored in secure facilities with access restricted to authorized personnel only. Although we make good faith efforts to store the Personal Information we collect in a secure operating environment that is not accessible to unauthorized users, we cannot guarantee complete security. 

To provide secure credit card processing when ordering from us, orders placed on our Website are processed through a payment gateway which operates under its own privacy policy. If you choose to purchase or license Website Builder Products or Services online using a credit card, the credit card information is sent to Website Builder using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption, an industry-standard method for protecting data as it travels over the Internet, or a similar encryption technology that may become accepted as an industry standard or better encryption method, in the future ("Transmission Encryption"). To learn more about our credit card processing vendors and their respective privacy and other policies (which are incorporated by reference into the Website Builder Privacy Policy and Terms or Use by reference) email us at [support@websitebuilder.com](mailto:support@websitebuilder.com). 

####  **How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information**

You can access selected Personal Information that we collect online by logging into your account via our home page. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your Personal Information on our Website or by sending a request, to [support@websitebuilder.com](mailto:support@websitebuilder.com), that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we take commercially reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

####  **Severability**

This Privacy Policy shall apply to the fullest extent permitted by applicable law. If for any reason any provision of this Privacy Policy is held to be invalid or unenforceable to any extent under applicable law, then (i) such provision will be interpreted, construed, or reformed to the extent reasonably required to render it valid, enforceable, and consistent with the original intent underlying such provision and (ii) such invalidity or unenforceability will not affect the validity or enforceability of any other provision of this Privacy Policy and all such provisions shall remain in full force and effect. 

####  **Changes to Privacy Policy**

Any changes we make to this Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. 

####  **Website Builder Contact information**

If you have any questions or comments, please contact us at [support@websitebuilder.com](mailto:support@websitebuilder.com). Although we strongly prefer email communication, you may also send regular postal mail to: 

Website Builder   
Unit 6, Fulcrum 2   
Solent Way, Whiteley   
Hampshire   
PO15 7FN   
United Kingdom
